Guide to the Norman Hackerman personal and professional papers, 1956-1986 MS 407
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IV: Business files
  - Corrosion Monographs Series #7: editorial corresp. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Corrosion Monographs Series #8: editorial corresp. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Zoned-refined iron sample (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Texas Tech long-range planning (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - "The United Nations comes to Texas" (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Interview: "Capital Eye," 8-10-70 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Reviews: Journal of Physical Chemistry (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Review: Comprehensive Treatise of Electrochemistry, Vol. 7 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Editorial: AAAS, 1-10-72 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Editorial: Science, 2-4-72 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Monograph: Corrosion inhibition (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Article: Science, 3-16-73 (Box 10, Folder 18)